A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, National Commission on Water Quality, Series 9 FA379
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Draft), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (2 of 4) Chapters IV-VIII, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1311)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Draft), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (3 of 4) Chapters IX-XI, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1312)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Draft), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (4 of 4) Chapters XII-XIII, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1313)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Final Report), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (1 of 4) Chapters I-III, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1314)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Final Report), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (2 of 4) Chapters IV-X, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1315)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Final Report), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (3 of 4) Chapters XI, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1316)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Final Report), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (4 of 4) Chapters XII-XIII, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1317)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Percy Priest Reservoir (Final Report), Vanderbilt University, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1318)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - St. John's River/Estuary (Exec. Summary, Draft), Atlantis Scientific, May 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1319)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - St. John's River/Estuary (Draft), Atlantis Scientific, May 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1320)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - St. John's River/Estuary (Final Report), Atlantis Scientific, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1321)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Utah Lake/Jordan River (Draft), Environmental Dynamics, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1322)
- Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Utah Lake/Jordan River (Final Report), Environmental Dynamics, December 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1323)
- Overall Studies - Municipal Wastewaters in Open Coastal Waters (Draft), Southern California Coastal Water Research Project, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1324)
- Overall Studies - Municipal Wastewaters in Open Coastal Waters (Final Report), Southern California Coastal Water Research Project, December 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1325)
- Overall Studies - Disposal of Wastewater Residuals, Vol. 1 of 2, Environmental Quality Systems, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1326)
- Overall Studies - Disposal of Wastewater Residuals, Vol. 2 of 2, Environmental Quality Systems, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1327)
- Overall Studies - Water Quality Evaluations, Hydroscience, December 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1328)
- Overall Studies - Compliance Monitoring (Draft), Energy Resources, June 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1329)
- Overall Studies - Construction Grants (Draft), Touche Ross, April 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1330)
- Overall Studies - Construction Grants (Final Report), Touche Ross, August 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1331)
- Overall Studies - Enforcement (Draft), Environmental Law Institute, April 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1332)
- Overall Studies - Enforcement (Final Report), Environmental Law Institute, July 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1333)
- Overall Studies - Pollution Discharge Elimination System (Permit System) (Draft), Energy and Environmental Analysis, May 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1334)
- Overall Studies - Pollution Discharge Elimination System (Permit System) (Final Report), Energy and Environmental Analysis, undated (Box 47, Folder 1335)
- Overall Studies - Planning Requirements (Draft), by Harold F. Wise, May 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1336)
- Overall Studies - Planning Requirements (Final Report), by Harold F. Wise, August 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1337)
- Overall Studies - Study Design, Elizabeth Haskell, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 1338)
- Overall Studies - Attitudes of Selected Groups (Draft), Oregon Research Institute, August 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1339)
- Overall Studies - Attitudes of Participants (Final Report), Oregon Research Institute, December 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1340)
- Overall Studies - Problems of Agriculture "Doers" (Draft), David Hartley and Victoria Price, July 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1341)
- Overall Studies - Problems of Agriculture "Doers" (Final Report), David Hartley and Victoria Price, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1342)
- Overall Studies - Problems of Municipal "Doers" (Draft), Victoria Price and David Hartley, July 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1343)
- Overall Studies - Problems of Municipal "Doers" (Final Report), Victoria Price and David Hartley, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1344)
- Overall Studies - Problems of Industrial "Doers" (Draft), Phillip Clark, July 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1345)
- Overall Studies - Legal Issues, Environmental and Safety Research Services, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1346)
- Overall Studies - Legal Issues: Tables and Appendices, Environmental and Safety Research Services, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1347)
- Overall Studies - Public Participation (Draft), by James Ragan Associates, June 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1348)
- Overall Studies - Public Participation (Final Report), by James Ragan Associates, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1349)
- Regional Reports - Delaware River Basin (Phase One Report), Betz Environmental Engineers, January 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1350)
- Regional Reports - Delaware River Basin (Draft, Vol. I), Betz Environmental Engineers, June 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1351)
- Regional Reports - Delaware River Basin (Draft, Vol. II), Betz Environmental Engineers, June 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1352)
- Regional Reports - Delaware River Basin (Final Report, Vol. I), Betz Environmental Engineers, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1353)
- Regional Reports - Delaware River Basin (Final Report, Vol. II), Betz Environmental Engineers, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1354)
- Regional Reports - Merrimack-Nashua River Basin (Draft, Vol. I), Abt Associates, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1355)
- Regional Reports - Merrimack-Nashua River Basin (Draft, Vol. II), Abt Associates, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1356)
- Regional Reports - Merrimack-Nashua River Basin (Final Report, Vol. I), Abt Associates, November 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1357)
- Regional Reports - Merrimack-Nashua River Basin (Final Report, Vol. II), Abt Associates, November 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1358)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Executive Summary (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1359)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. I (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1360)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapters 1-3 (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1361)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapter 4 (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1362)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapters 5-7 (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1363)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapter 8 (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1364)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. I, Part I (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1365)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. I, Part II, Chapter 1 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1366)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. I, Part II, Chapter 2 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1367)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. I, Part II, Chapter 3 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1368)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapter 4 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1369)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapters 5-6 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1370)
- Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapters 7-8 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1371)
- Regional Reports - Lake Erie, Vol. I (Draft), Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1372)
- Regional Reports - Lake Erie, Vol. II (Draft), Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1373)
- Regional Reports - Lake Erie, Vol. III (Draft), Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1374)
- Regional Reports - Lake Erie, (Final Report), Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport, December 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1375)
- Regional Reports - Lake Erie, Appendices I-V (Final Report), Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport, December 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1376)
- Regional Reports - Lake Erie, Appendices VI-VII (Final Report), Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport, December 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1377)
- Regional Reports - Kanawha River Basin (Draft), Executive Summary, Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1378)
- Regional Reports - Kanawha River Basin (Draft), Vol. I, Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1379)
- Regional Reports - Kanawha River Basin (Draft), Vol. II, Chapters 1-3, Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1380)
- Regional Reports - Kanawha River Basin (Draft), Vol. II, Chapter 4, Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1381)
- Regional Reports - Kanawha River Basin (Draft), Vol. II, Chapter 5, Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1382)
- Regional Reports - Kanawha River Basin (Draft), Vol. II, Chapter 6, Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1383)
- Regional Reports - Kanawha River Basin (Final Report), Executive Summary and Part I: Summary Report, Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1384)
- Regional Reports - Kanawha River Basin (Final Report), Part II - Main Report, Chapters 1-2, Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1385)
- Regional Reports - Kanawha River Basin (Final Report), Part II, Chapters 3-4, Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1386)
- Regional Reports - Kanawha River Basin (Final Report), Part II, Chapter 5, Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1387)
- Regional Reports - Kanawha River Basin (Final Report), Part II, Chapter 6, Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1388)
- Regional Reports - Chattahoochee-Flint-Apalachicola, Phase II Draft Report, Part I, Hammer, Siler, George Associates, July 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1389)
- Regional Reports - Chattahoochee-Flint-Apalachicola, Phase II Draft Report, Part II, Volume I, Hammer, Siler, George Associates, July 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1390)
- Regional Reports - Chattahoochee-Flint-Apalachicola, Phase II Draft Report, Part II, Volume II, Hammer, Siler, George Associates, July 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1391)
- Regional Reports - Chattahoochee-Flint-Apalachicola, Phase II Final Report, Part I, Hammer, Siler, George Associates, December 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1392)
- Regional Reports - Chattahoochee-Flint-Apalachicola, Phase II Final Report, Part II, Volume I, Hammer, Siler, George Associates, December 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1393)
- Regional Reports - Chattahoochee-Flint-Apalachicola, Phase II Final Report, Part II, Volume II, Hammer, Siler, George Associates, December 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1394)
- Regional Reports - Houston Ship Channel/Galveston Bay (Draft), Part I, Bernard Johnson Incorporated, June 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1395)
- Regional Reports - Houston Ship Channel/Galveston Bay (Draft), Part II, Chapters I-V, Bernard Johnson Incorporated, June 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1396)
- Regional Reports - Houston Ship Channel/Galveston Bay (Draft), Part II, Chapters VI-VIII and Bibliography, Bernard Johnson Incorporated, June 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1397)
- Regional Reports - Houston Ship Channel/Galveston Bay (Final Report), Vol. I, Bernard Johnson Incorporated, August 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1398)
- Regional Reports - Houston Ship Channel/Galveston Bay (Final Report), Vol. II, Bernard Johnson Incorporated, August 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1399)
- Regional Reports - Houston Ship Channel/Galveston Bay (Final Report), Vol. III, Bernard Johnson Incorporated, August 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1400)
- Regional Reports - Colorado River (Draft), Utah State University, March 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1401)
- Regional Reports - Colorado River, Part I - Executive Summary, Basin Profile, Report Digest, Utah State University, October 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1401A)
- Regional Reports - Colorado River, Part II - Detailed Analyses, Utah State University, October 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1402)
- Regional Reports - Colorado River, Part III - Water Quality Analysis, Utah State University, October 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1403)
- Regional Reports - Colorado River, Part IV - Bibliography and Appendices, Utah State University, October 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1404)
- Regional Reports - San Francisco Bay - Central Valley, Phase 1 Report, Arthur D. Little, February 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1405)
- Regional Reports - San Francisco Bay - Central Valley (Draft), Vol. I - Summary and Conclusions, Arthur D. Little, June 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1406)
- Regional Reports - San Francisco Bay - Central Valley (Draft), Vol. II - Data, Methodology, and Detailed Analyses, Arthur D. Little, June 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1407)
- Regional Reports - San Francisco Bay - Central Valley (Final Report), Vol. I - Summary and Conclusions, Arthur D. Little, November 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1408)
- Regional Reports - San Francisco Bay - Central Valley (Final Report), Vol. II - Data, Methodology, and Detailed Analyses, Arthur D. Little, November 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1409)
- Regional Reports - Yellowstone River Basin, Executive Summary of Interim Report, Stevens, Thompson and Runyan, February 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1410)
- Regional Reports - Yellowstone River Basin (Draft), Vol. I, Stevens, Thompson, and Runyan, June 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1411)
- Regional Reports - Yellowstone River Basin (Draft), Vol. II, Stevens, Thompson, and Runyan, June 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1412)
- Regional Reports - Yellowstone River Basin (Draft), Vol. II Supplement, Stevens, Thompson and Runyan, June 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1413)
- Regional Reports - Yellowstone River Basin (Final Report), Stevens, Thompson and Runyan, March 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1414)
- Regional Reports - Puget Sound (Draft), Vol. I, Stevens, Thompson and Runyan, June 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1415)
- Regional Reports - Puget Sound (Draft), Vol. II, Stevens, Thompson and Runyan, June 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1416)
- Regional Reports - Puget Sound (Draft), Vol. II Supplement, Stevens, Thompson and Runyan, June 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1417)
- Regional Reports - Puget Sound (Final Report), Stevens, Thompson and Runyan, March 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1418)
- Regional Reports - Reconnaissance Survey of Available Information, Chapters 1-5 & Appendices 1-2, Electronic Data Systems, July 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1419)
- Regional Reports - Reconnaissance Survey of Available Information, Appendices 3-10, Electronic Data Systems, July 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1420)
- Regional Reports - Reconnaissance Survey of Available Information, Appendices 11-14, Electronic Data Systems, July 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1421)
- Regional Reports- Illustrative Framework Plan for Regional Assessment Studies (Second Draft), Arthur D. Little, April 1974 (Box 53, Folder 1422)
- Regional Reports - Technology Costs, National Academy of Sciences, January and February 1974 (Box 53, Folder 1423)
- Regional Reports - Water Reuse and Secondary Treatment, National Academy of Sciences, February 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1424)
- Regional Reports - Comments on November 1975 Staff Report, National Academy of Sciences, January 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1425)
- Regional Reports - Review and Comment on Final Staff Report of April 1976, National Academy of Sciences, November 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1426)
- Regional Reports - Residuals Discharge Inventory, National Research Council, January 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1427)
- Regional Reports - Scheduling and Monitoring, Linton, Mields, and Coston, December 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1428)
- Regional Reports - Issues and Problems, Linton, Mields, and Coston, December 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1429)
- Regional Reports - Assessment of Modeling and Indirect Benefit Indicators, Linton, Mields, and Coston, December 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1430)
- Regional Reports - International Aspects of Environmental Policies, Jeno Vegh, April 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1431)
- Regional Reports - Economic and Social Studies, Howard Cook, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 1432)
- Regional Reports - Comments on Commission's Draft Report, Arthur Inerfield, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 1433)
- Regional Reports - Overlapping Jurisdictions, Arthur Inerfield, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 1434)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Concept of Benefits in Benefit-Cost Analysis, Robert Haveman and Burton Weisbrod, September 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1435)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Techniques for Measuring Benefits of Water Quality Improvements, Myrick Freeman, September 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1436)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Voting, Cost-Benefit Analysis, and Water Pollution, Paul Portney, September 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1437)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Some Institutional And Conceptual Thoughts, John Bishop and Charles Cicchetti, September 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1438)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Valuing Long Run Ecological Consequences, Anthony Fisher and John Krutilla, September 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1439)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Survey of Empirical Benefit Studies, Dennis Tihansky, September 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1440)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Costs of Water Quality Improvement, Allen Kneese, September 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1441)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Techniques for Measuring Control Costs, Robert Davis and John Boland, September 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1442)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Quantifying Public Policy Costs, Ralph d'Arge, September 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1443)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Cost-Benefit Analysis, Property-Right Specification, and "Distribution," J.A. Stockfisch, September 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1444)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Pragmatic Strategies for the Design of Water Pollution Control Institutions, Thomas Crocker, September 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1445)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Ignorance, Monopoly, and Uncertainty, Mancur Olson, Jr., September 1973 (Box 54, Folder 1446)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Project-by-Project Analysis vs. Comprehensive Planning, Fred Abel, September 1973 (Box 54, Folder 1447)
- Papers From Environmental Protection Agency Symposium: "Cost-Benefit Analysis and Pollution Control Policy" - Role of Cost-Benefit Analysis in Policy-Making, Henry Rowen, September 1973 (Box 54, Folder 1448)
- Contract Materials, June 1974 (Box 54, Folder 1449)
- Executive Committee, November 26, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 1450)
  NAR Presiding
- Miscellaneous Correspondence #1 (Box 54, Folder 1451)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence #2 (Box 54, Folder 1452)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence #3 (Box 54, Folder 1453)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence #4 (Box 54, Folder 1454)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence #5 (Box 54, Folder 1455)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence #6 (Box 54, Folder 1456)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence #7 (Box 54, Folder 1457)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence and NAR Clippings #8 (Box 54, Folder 1458)
- 1 Extra Copy of Staff Report to Commission, April 1976 (Box 54, Folder 1459)
- National Commission on Water Quality Report to United States Congress, 1970 March 18 (Box 55)
  Existence and Location of Copies
  Box contains 70 extra copies of report
- Comparative Print, House/Senate Bills - Used by Conferees, Title I - Title III (Box 56, Folder 869)
  Oversized Material
- Comparative Print, House/Senate Bills - Used by Conferees, Title IV, V (Box 56, Folder 870)
- Prof. Harvey Lieber's Book, "Federalism and Clean Water" Table of Contents - Chapter 3 (Box 56, Folder 891)
- Prof. Harvey Lieber's Book, "Federalism and Clean Water" Table of Contents - Chapter 4-Conclusion (Box 56, Folder 892)